{
  "id": "flashcard-english-5-unit-5",
  "title": "Tiếng Anh Lớp 5 - Unit 5",
  "subject": "english",
  "tags": [
    "grade5",
    "unit5",
    "vocab"
  ],
  "description": "Từ vựng Unit 5: My future job",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "doctor",
      "answer": "bác sĩ",
      "speak": "doctor"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "firefighter",
      "answer": "lính cứu hỏa",
      "speak": "firefighter"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "reporter",
      "answer": "phóng viên",
      "speak": "reporter"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "gardener",
      "answer": "người làm vườn",
      "speak": "gardener"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "writer",
      "answer": "nhà văn",
      "speak": "writer"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "job fair",
      "answer": "hội chợ việc làm",
      "speak": "job fair"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "artist",
      "answer": "nghệ sĩ",
      "speak": "artist"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "dentist",
      "answer": "nha sĩ",
      "speak": "dentist"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "farmer",
      "answer": "nông dân",
      "speak": "farmer"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "prefer",
      "answer": "thích hơn",
      "speak": "prefer"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "survey",
      "answer": "khảo sát",
      "speak": "survey"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "take care of",
      "answer": "chăm sóc",
      "speak": "take care of"
    }
  ]
}